stanforddaily.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | The Stanford Daily

The Stanford Daily, and its advertisers, take seriously your security as you turn to our site for news about the Stanford community.

When you visit our site, The Stanford Daily does not collect personally identifiable information about you without your permission (for example, name, address, or email address.) The Stanford Daily does at times, however, collect non-personally identifiable, such as your Internet Service Provider and the type of browser, monitor and computer operating system you are using to access our site. We use this information to improve our website experience and customer service, as well as to personalize your experience.

You may visit our site anonymously and you may comment under the name “anonymous” or something similar, though we encourage you to identify yourself and prohibit you from impersonating another, including another commenter, Stanford Daily employee, or subject of Daily content. When you comment on our site, you provide us with your IP address.

We do collect personal information if you choose to subscribe to our print edition or to our email digest. To subscribe to our print edition, you will be asked to provide your full name, phone number, mailing address and email address, in addition to payment information. To subscribe to our email digest, you must provide your first name and email address, though you may be asked for additional information, such as your Stanford affiliation.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) and typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, please visit: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp  

We are in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act (effective as of July 1, 2004) and will not distribute personal information to outside parties without your consent. We occasionally link to third party sites. We are not liable for the content or privacy policies of these sites, but welcome feedback about our linking practices. We do occasionally transfer non-personally identifiable information to outside parties for advertising and marketing purposes, or other similar uses. This includes trusted third parties who work with us in operating our website and conducting our business and who agree to keep this information confidential.

We may release your information to comply with the law (when we respond to subpoenas, court order or legal process), to enforce our site policies, or to protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect any information from persons under 13 years of age.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be immediately updated on this page.

All content on our website is copyrighted by The Stanford Daily Publishing Corporation. Upon viewing our website you agree not to reproduce or republish our content except with express written permission.

The privacy policy for our partnership with Ezoic may be found at the following URL: <https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/stanforddaily.com>

## Contact Us

If you have additional questions or concerns about The Stanford Daily’s efforts to protect your privacy, please contact the Chief Operating Officer at coo ‘at’ stanforddaily.com.

You may also contact us at:

456 Panama Mall

Stanford, CA 94305
